Contact

sheheryar.ahmad@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sheheryar-ahmad (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

.NET Core ASP.NET Web API ASP.NET MVC

Languages

English

Urdu (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Java + Android

Honors-Awards

Employee Of The Month Employee Of The Month Employee Of The Month Employee Of The Quarter

Sheheryar Ahmad

Sr. Software Engineer | .NET Core | AWS Pakistan

Summary

My objective is to work in a company where I can utilize my knowledge, skills and abilities that offers professional growth while being resourceful and flexible. I want to make significant contribution to the organization by hard work and constant performance at every stage of my life and contribute significantly through the assigned task. To secure a promising position which allows me to grow professionally while earning a good reputation amongst my peers.

- Having 4.5 years of experience in C#, Asp.Net MVC and Asp.Net Core.
- Worked on Project management tools to control the flow of task and power up the team development process.
- Proficient in maintaining and backup source code using version control systems like Github.
- Knowledge and working on CI/CD.

Experience

QuantumLHE (pvt) Ltd.
Software Engineer
November 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month)
Lahore, Pakistan

Work as a core part of the Backend team for the mobile application. Designing a new microservice architecture, modifying and optimizing the existing one and always looked for work enhancements for efficiency and effectiveness.

Softech Systems (Private) Limited Software Engineer January 2017 - November 2019 (2 years 11 months) Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

Worked as a Backend and Frontend development for MVC based Web and Rest API's project.

Education

Superior University
Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science · (2012 - 2016)